zoomtown.com 2015-08-12

# Cincinnati Bell Privacy Policy Cincinnati

Cincinnati Bell, Inc. and its subsidiary and affiliated entities (collectively, "Cincinnati Bell") knows how important personal privacy is to our customers. Cincinnati Bell maintains strict privacy policies and uses industry-accepted technologies to safeguard such information. 

As part of our commitment to our customers, Cincinnati Bell has adopted the following comprehensive Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to information we have collected about you in connection with the products and services we provide to you. However, some of our services have specific privacy policies, such as Fuse, ZoomTown, and cable services. In the event of a conflict between this Privacy Policy and a service-specific Privacy Policy, the terms of the service-specific Privacy Policy will control. 

This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms of Use posted on our Website, sets forth the general rules, policies and procedures governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions. 

This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes those policies and procedures, as well as how we collect and use various types of information. We encourage you to read this Policy in its entirety. 

### Information Collection 

The information we collect depends on what you do when you visit our web site. There are two types of information that we are likely to record: 

  * **Non-personally identifiable information collected in the aggregate:** We collect various "anonymous" facts each time you visit our site. This information includes the date and time you access our site, the internet address you use, what page(s) on the site you visited, the type of browser you use, etc. We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site and to help us make our site more useful to visitors. 
  * **Personally identifiable information you give us:** We collect the personally identifiable information you provide directly to us in the course of conducting business on our web site. This information can include name, e-mail address, credit card numbers, etc. Except as otherwise provided below, this personally identifiable information is only used to conduct business with you, provide you with specific services and communicate with you. We may also use this information to send you e-mails about new products and services. If you create a personal account with us and provide us with the above information for the purpose of conducting business, you authorize us to store your name, shipping address, credit card and billing information.

### How We Use Your Information

#### Personally Identifiable Information.

We may use your personally identifiable information for the following business purposes:

  * To ensure that you are receiving the services you ordered
  * To allow us to properly maintain those services and to make improvements or upgrades when necessary
  * To confirm that you are being properly billed
  * To provide you with technical support and for system maintenance
  * To inform you of new products or services that may be of interest to you
  * To us to understand the use of, and identify improvements to, our services
  * To prevent fraud, including the unauthorized use of our service or violations of applicable policies and terms of service
  * To ensure our own compliance with the law 

Additionally, we may use or disclose personally identifiable information about you without your consent to protect our customers, employees, or property, in emergency situations, to enforce our rights under our terms of service and policies, in court or elsewhere. Further, we may disclose your personally identifiable information where necessary to provide or conduct a legitimate business activity related to the services provided to you or as required as required by law or legal process. 

We do not sell, trade or rent your personally identifiable information to outside companies or marketing firms, except for the following circumstances. We may share this information within the family of Cincinnati Bell-affiliated companies to improve our services to you. We may also share personally identifiable customer information with our agents and trusted business partners when required for the specific and limited purposes of providing products or services to you that you have authorized, such as to our shipper in order to fulfill an on-line order, as well as to evaluate and improve the quality of our services.

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

This information is data about usage and Services operation that is not associated with a specific personal identity. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser and the type of computer operating system you are using. We collect and analyze non-personally identifiable information to evaluate how visitors use our Web site and enhance visitors' online experience. Most non-personally identifiable data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. 

### Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

A cookie is a small text file created by our web site and stored on your computer that assists us in providing customized services. The use of cookies is a standard in the industry and you'll find they're used at most web sites. We use cookies for login verification, session management, load balancing and personalization to enable your user experience. We never use cookies to retrieve non-public personally identifiable information from your computer that was not already voluntarily provided to us by you. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case, you may not be able to use certain features on our site, including the "My Account" self service functionality. Click here to learn how to enable or disable cookies on your computer. 

### How We Protect and Preserve Customer Privacy 

Cincinnati Bell uses industry standard practices to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, including firewalls and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption. Cincinnati Bell treats data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by users inside and outside the company.

To help ensure the confidentiality of your personal information, it is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

### Linked Web Sites

Cincinnatibell.com is a web site that contains links to various other web sites. Please be aware that these other sites may have privacy policies that differ from Cincinnati Bell's policies. Cincinnati Bell assumes no responsibility for either the content that appears on linked sites or your privacy once you have linked to other sites. 

### How You May Use our Materials, Marks and Informational Content

Click here to read our legal statements regarding use of Cincinnati Bell Proprietary Information.

### Customer Proprietary Network Information (CPNI)

The Telecommunications Act and federal regulations give you, the customer, a choice about how Cincinnati Bell uses information about your current telecommunications services to provide information to you about new or additional products and services that will best meet your communication needs. These regulations are designed to protect your privacy rights as a telecommunications customer.

Cincinnati Bell values our customers' privacy and meeting your communication needs is our top priority. Under federal law, you have the right to authorize use or non-use of your CPNI by Cincinnati Bell companies including Cincinnati Bell Inc., Cincinnati Bell Telephone, Cincinnati Bell Wireless, Cincinnati Bell Any Distance, Cincinnati Bell Extended Territories, eVolve Business Solutions LLC and agents and authorized sales representatives of Cincinnati Bell. CPNI is data that is not publicly available and includes information such as type of service, number of telephone lines, amount of usage, and calling and billing records. [Click here](http://www.cincinnatibell.com/customer_support/policies/customer_proprietary_network_information/) to read more about CPNI or to authorize use or non-use of your CPNI.

### Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We generally keep this Privacy Policy posted on our Website and you should review it frequently, as it may change from time to time without notice. Cincinnati Bell will post online any changes to this Privacy Policy on or before the effective date of the change. You will be able to determine the date of the last change by noting the effective date of the policy above. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be prospective only and will not affect information collected prior to the effective date of the change in the Privacy Policy. WHEN YOU ACCESS OUR WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, IMMEDIATELY STOP ACCESSING OUR WEBSITE.
